{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521288131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521288131"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 2590348f-31aa-435f-8b30-84a8a5b1e793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua_vyema-chuma-maua-pembe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521329847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521329847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 2590348f-31aa-435f-8b30-84a8a5b1e793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbaazi_mlio-muhimu-ladha-mbaazi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbaazi"," userResponse":" mbaazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521371385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521371385"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 2590348f-31aa-435f-8b30-84a8a5b1e793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbaazi_msimu-dogo-kucha-mbaazi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbaazi"," userResponse":" mbaazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521389834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521389833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 2590348f-31aa-435f-8b30-84a8a5b1e793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mbaazi_msimu-dogo-kucha-mbaazi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521389973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521389973"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 2590348f-31aa-435f-8b30-84a8a5b1e793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521398744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521398744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 879a651e-a66f-470c-a3a6-d1c2c1ebe802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-K-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521404443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521404443"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 879a651e-a66f-470c-a3a6-d1c2c1ebe802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-K-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521407390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521407389"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 879a651e-a66f-470c-a3a6-d1c2c1ebe802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-K-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521419676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521419676"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-8-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521426308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521426308"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_6-1-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521431068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521431067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_6-1-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521438719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521438719"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-2-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521459043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521459043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-2-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521467300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521467300"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-6-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521472777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521472777"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-6-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521479791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521479791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521485140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521485140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521490724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521490724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-8-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521496575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521496575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-8-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521501383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521501383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521507611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521507611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521513823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521513823"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-0-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521518840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521518840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-0-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521524968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521524968"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-0-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521530857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521530857"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-0-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521537399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521537398"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" b88b1fd6-d355-45ab-a54a-521a39f6aaff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.rise.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-0-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521548470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521548469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-A-F"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521551436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521551436"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521556724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521556724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521560141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521560141"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-U-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521562982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521562981"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_H-P-I"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521568268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521568268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_H-P-I"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521571440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521571439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_G-E-I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521574560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521574560"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-J-I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521577844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521577844"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_E-I-T"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521584904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521584904"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_E-I-T"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521588316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521588316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_Z-I-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548521589541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548521589541"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_194655"," gameId":" 42f47f6d-83f3-4d5b-bf15-07b737a05148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_Z-I-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}